Brought to you by DLAznMovies. com
Fansubbed by Shadowlord
So you're here, after all?
It's food.
Eat it.
It's a gratuitous
service from the landlady.
When I look at you,
you're pretty...
Don't mind me.
You're an abandoned
Goze, right?
So you know the
taste of men, right?
I don't know what I don't cut.
Because I'm blind.
I'm not really interested
in a love affair with a man.
But...
wouldn't it be nice to be warmed
by someone in a cold night?
Women who can see consider
their appearance to be important.
But we don't care.
But still, we Goze...
are being chased away from our
comrades if we get involved with men.
Oh well...
What a strange law!
If no one gives us warmth,...
we have to to
freeze to death...
Hey.
Are you listening?
You've got involved
with men, too, right?
Am I right?
Hey!
Someone has come!
You know that I can't see,
so don't make fun of me!
What?
Give me the money as agreed.
Shut up!
Pay!
Hey.
There's another one.
What a beautiful
woman, brother!
Let's see...
Yes.
Are you a Goze, too?
My brother has asked
you something! Answer!
Please don't mind me.
What're you sayin'?
Don't mind me.
Oh, whatever,
come with me! Hey!
Wait!
Wait a second!
Don't you see that
she doesn't want to?
Yeah.
What do you want...
I'm just a transient.
Would you please do me a
favor and leave her alone?
Wai... wai... wai...
wai... wai... wait,
wait, wait! Wait!
Don't let us shed
blood uselessly.
Wait a second!
Let's have a deal.
What about this?
It's a promissory
note, worth ten ryou.
It's a real one.
You think you'll save
her, if you give us money?
Brother, if we kill him, we'll
get the ten ryou and the woman!
That's mean!
What's wrong?
Come!
What are you doing, bitch?!
Hey!
You!
Hey. What's your name?
Maybe I should
introduce myself first.
I'm Touma Fujihira
from Shimousa.
Right now, I'm just
wandering around.
I'm traveling in the
pursuit of knowledge.
But when I saved you...
my promissory note
got ripped apart, so...
I have to find a job now
and earn some money...
or I cannot
continue my journey.
Well, I have quite a lot of
self-confidence in my skills.
A job as a bodyguard or
something similar would be nice...
You've saved me?
Well, even though
you've killed them...
I could've defeated
those guys alone.
Huh.
You've laughed, right?
You've laughed.
"Huh?" You've laughed
at me with a "huh".
I cannot let you get away
after mocking a samurai!
Who is this woman?
Goze, I'll show
you a nice inn.
Where's the gambling den?
The gambling den is
outside the inn town, but...
I'll lead you there!
Do you want to gamble, Goze?
Do you want to stay
here for tonight?
Are you ready?
I'll roll the dice.
Make your bets.
Chou.
Han.
No one seems to know him.
No more han?
Chou.
Make your bets.
Han.
The bets are set. Win or loss.
Two and four, chou.
Oh!
The Banki gang...
Almost no money left...
What a loudmouth.
Hey!
I can't concentrate when
you're standing there!
Come here. Do you
want to challenge me?
So...
Let us continue.
Are you ready?
I'll roll the dice.
Make your bets.
Chou.
Han.
Make your bets.
Yes. No one says chou?
Chou.
Han.
Anyone else?
Make your bets.
Chou.
Make your bets!
Yes. No one says chou?
Yes, make your bets.
Chou.
The bets are set.
Five and three, chou.
Han.
Make your bets.
Yes. No one says chou?
It's han!
Anyone else? Make your bets.
Chou.
Han.
The bets are set.
Win or loss.
Four and one, han.
Here it comes...
Chou.
So, make your bets.
Make your bets.
Chou.
Two and six, chou.
Next, next!
Yeah, another round!
OK, let's continue.
I'll start.
I don't need any light.
Oh, right.
But while you're
at the inn town...
I'll see for you,
so be unconcerned.
Thank you.
I've got ten ryou.
So I've paid my debt.
Boy.
Because I've got a lot of money now,
could you please lead me to a decent inn?
Don't call me
boy. I'm Kotarou.
Hey, wait! Wait!
Wait, I said wait!
What do you want?
You! How dare you to
make fools out of us?
We didn't do anything...
You must've
tricked us somehow.
We didn't do anything unfair.
Give us our money back. That's
the only way to save your life.
I refuse.
What?!
If you want my money, you
have to take it by force!
What?!
Yeah!
Don't interfere this time.
Look, he's shaking.
How pathetic.
Come and get me!
Die!
Thank you again!
Wow...
Oh, there they are!
Are they already dead?!
You're great, huh?
Five men with
just one sword...
That serves those
Banki gangsters right!
Banki gang?
They're a hostile gang,
freeloading on our inn town.
You're very talented.
I'm Toraji from the Shirakawa group and I'm
responsible for this inn town called Bitou.
Master, I want to hire
you as a bodyguard.
What?
I'll pay you well.
What about twenty ryou?
No, no, no...
Isn't it enough?
OK, I know you're very good...
So what about thirty ryou?
Thirty ryou.
Toraji.
OK, it's settled.
What's your name, master?
I'm Touma Fujihira.
Tonma? (Note: means "fool")
Idiot. It's Touma.
Kotarou.
Have you brought him here?
Yes!
You did a great job. I'll
buy you dumplings tomorrow.
Oh, Goze, wait!
Is she your companion?
No, not really...
I see.
OK, this way, master.
Let's go. After you, master.
It's this way. Please...
You're really good, miss.
I'm sure you can finish
the Banki off easily!
But are you fine with this? It was
you, who killed them, after all...
You really don't want
to stay in an inn?
A shrine or something
like that would be enough.
Come with me, then.
It's not very far.
Right!
My father says he knows
a blind laido master.
I'm back, father!
Who is this woman?
She's a Goze. She's
searching someone...
Have you lied again and
brought a woman here?
Father!
Heh, you're
definitely a woman.
But aren't you even
dirtier than me?!
Don't make fun of me!
Don't kill dad!
It seems he really
wants to have a mother...
But I don't really need one.
Oh, no... This story...
Oh, yes, yes. And...
In three days,
Kataoka Hasshuu will...
come to the Bitou Inn.
If everything goes well,
he'll beat the Banki gang...
The Shirakawa are putting
much effort in this!
And among these
performers and...
Kabuki actors which
they've also called,...
is a blind laido master.
That ronin did that?
How?
Boss.
Their wounds look the same like
those of the guys we've found before.
A straight line, caused
by a backhand grip.
I didn't know...
that there's still someone left
who has mastered this technique...
Oh, master...
Here, drink!
Good, good, good.
That I'm getting
served by the boss...
What? You don't
have to hold off.
And the boss is my
father, Choubee Shirakawa.
Hey, everyone!
Because Fujihira has come to us,
there's nothing we need to fear anymore.
Yes!
He's the guy who has
slaughtered five Banki members!
Yeah!
I'm different from my father!
I don't want to stay silent while
we are despised by the Banki!
I'm Toraji from
the Shirakawa group.
Yeah!
And now drink and eat a lot!
Oh, you too, master.
Oh, Kihachi.
Have you brought her here?
Yes...
Oh, we've been
waiting for this!
Oh.
You're a pretty
beautiful Goze, huh?
What's your name?
My name is Ichi.
What do you want to hear?
What, master?
Oh, no... I don't
know any songs...
Play something adequate.
Yes.
If my mother doesn't
sing for me tonight
I cannot sleep, when I'm
cradled on their knees
No, no, no. Hey!
I didn't mean
something like that.
Play something with a
more positive atmosphere.
Play something on your Shamisen
that will motivate our master.
Yes.
Oh, this is it! This one!
Hey, master.
Kotarou?
It's me, Touma Fujihira.
Sorry, sorry. Did
you have to wait long?
Oh, Tonma.
It's Touma!
Toraji gave you
a lot of money!
Are you listening, miss?
You did a good job, right?
Use this as an eye bandage.
Hm, he has a strange taste.
You're a greedy woman.
It's business, after all.
And don't make the
mistake to touch his face!
Or you'll never
do business again!
Oh, master...
You haven't tried
anything yet.
Don't you like it?
Oh, no. That's not the case.
Since the Banki are here...
the Bitou Inn has
become quite desolated.
When Choubee was
healthy back then...
this was quite a
flourishing inn town.
If this goes on, the
Bitou Inn will be finished!
But if you kill the Banki...
Everyone in this inn town
is begging you to do this.
So eat a lot and
fortify yourself!
Eat a lot, OK?
Eat a lot.
Where's the toilet?
At the end of the floor.
I cannot stand
this much longer.
This would just be
useless bloodshedding.
We won't know if
we don't try it.
To invite Hasshuu...
and get an repression corps sent
here should be the best solution.
Are the preparations for
his hospitality being done?
Sure, the preparations
are being done.
But isn't it useless to rely
on a government official?
But no matter how many persons of
doubtful origin you try to gather...
they would be not
match for the Banki.
Master!
Not there! Here!
Good timing.
Father.
This is Fujihira.
He is far from being a
person of doubtful origin.
We depend on you.
Let's have a talk.
The Banki aren't
normal scoundrels.
They once were a group
of famous samurai...
They were so talented that
they were recommended...
as the swordplay
instructors of the bakufu.
Why does this man
has it in for you?
Once, his face got
severely burned...
There's a rumor that you cannot
look directly at him anymore.
Because of his
appearance, he finally...
had been chased away from
his official position...
And why...
The Banki gang...
decide whether we live or die and
they take from us whatever they want.
But they've already reached the limit
of this. I'm sure the Banki know that.
So...
I'm sure they'll just laugh
about our useless hospitality.
Really, I'm scared!
I love Toraji.
I'm really scared
that I'll lose him.
It seems he doesn't
want to grow old.
He's an excellent
father, right?
I have an excellent
father, I guess.
That he decided to try a
completely different method...
Here.
This is an insider
tip from Choubee.
Oh no! I've
forgotten the float.
Wait here, miss.
I'll go and get it.
Oh, Tonma!
Kotarou seems to like you.
Do you like children?
I hate them.
They're troublesome...
and noisy.
But...
they aren't as dirty as adults,
so it's easier to trust them.
Adults are dirty?
Most of them.
It took the bait.
Really?
I don't feel anything.
Oh, ah, no... oh... this is...
Here it comes! It's
pulling, it's pulling!
How could this happen...
If my mother doesn't
sing for me tonight
I cannot sleep, when I'm
cradled on their knees
This is the song
you've sung yesterday.
How does it go on?
Even though I've
been abandoned...
and I don't know his face...
But I don't hate him.
I want to meet him again.
You don't hate him?
I would love to
hear it completely.
Maybe there'll
be an opportunity.
Do you intend to stay in
this inn town for a while?
Until I've found him.
I see...
Soon...
the Shirakawa group and the Banki
gang might cross their swords.
Do you intend to help them?
You know, I'm the bodyguard
of the Shirakawa group.
You want to interfere...
What?
But if you don't do that in a moderate
way, you'll get in a lot of trouble.
Like you?
I cannot look away when
my comrades are in trouble.
If I were as
skilled as you are...
I'm sure I could've
saved the battered Goze.
I don't know what
happened to you before,...
but why are you so much afraid of
being involved with other people?
People who cannot see...
don't know what borders are.
They don't know whether
it's noon or night...
or where the way they're
walking on is suddenly ending...
They cannot see the borders.
They are afraid
because they cannot see.
Who is bad and who is good...
Where's the border
between them?
I don't even know that.
Whether I'm living or dying...
I cannot see
even that clearly!
I don't really think...
that I want to live anyway.
Wait!
Fight with me using this.
Stop it, Tonma.
You are no match for her.
Let's start!
Everything seems to
be proceeding well.
I'm sure this will
make Hasshuu very happy.
Yes.
Well, I hope this will
go for the Banki, too.
So that they'll be quiet while
Hasshuu resides in this inn town.
Sorry, I've accidentally put
too much strength into it.
Does it hurt?
You're even stronger
than her, Tonma.
Yes. I'm strong.
But that's just with a stick.
I can't draw a katana.
What do you mean by that?
I...
was born in the house of a martial
arts instructor of the Odaka clan.
Touma!
Mother!
She didn't die, but...
she had lost her eyesight.
Since then...
I cannot draw my katana.
But with a wooden
sword I can't lose.
I had a lot of
self-confidence in my skills.
But he thought
that it would be...
a shame for the family, if the successor of
an instructor couldn't draw his sword anymore.
After that, my father
started to dislike me.
Five years ago, my father
adopted his best disciple...
and passed the
inheritance on to him.
And I went on a journey in
the pursuit of knowledge.
This is my current situation.
Only my mother was kind to
me, even after she went blind.
She always dreamed that
I would become a Samurai...
and that's why she
always motivated me.
When I was fifteen, my mother
died because of an illness.
Even though she was seriously ill,
she desperately tried to live on.
Even though she was blind.
She didn't give up
her hope to live on.
She wanted to live on...
But that wish
didn't come true.
This...
This is how I am.
Hasshuu has arrived!
Hey, please hurry, everyone!
Really?
So the person you were
looking for isn't here?
Are you leaving the inn town?
Let's go!
They've lied.
Boss!